Guide to the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing Alumnae Association records 2014.006
Brooklyn Historical Society
Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing Alumnae Association records
1858-2014
Brooklyn Historical Society
Long Island College Hospital. School of Nursing
Long Island College Hospital. School of Nursing. Alumnae Association
2014.006
13 Linear Feet in 31 boxes of various sizes, one oversize folder,
5.24 Gigabytes in 878 digital files
The collection consists of the records of the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing Alumnae Association, as well as material which was collected by the association, dating from 1858 to 2014. This includes photographs, yearbooks, newsletters, college catalogs, event-related ephemera, and memorabilia. The collection documents the history of the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing, from its inception in 1883 to its closing in 2013.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing Alumnae Association, 2014.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of the records of the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing Alumnae Association, as well as material which was collected by the association, dating from 1858 to 2014. This includes photographs, yearbooks, newsletters, college catalogs, event-related ephemera, and memorabilia. The collection documents the history of the Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing, from its inception in 1883 to its closing in 2013.
The records document the lives of nursing students from the late 19th century to the early 20th century. Aspects of student life are illustrated extensively in the school's yearbooks, newsletters, and photographs. Special events, such as commencements and student recognition ceremonies (pinnings and cappings), are especially well documented. Some objects which belonged to students, such as nursing caps and commemorative pins, are also included in the collection.
The adminstration of the Alumnae Association is also documented in the collection. Researchers interested in the operations of the organization should consult Series 1: Articles of incorporation and by-laws, Series 2: Board of Directors meeting minutes, Series 3: Subject files series, and Series 6: Newsletters.
Nursing education and the school's curriculum is not extensively documented in the collection, although a small sampling of student work and handbooks can be found in Series 8: Students, alumni, and faculty and Series 10: Handbooks.
Separated Materials
The following volumes have been removed to the library's book collection:
Brooklyn First: A Chronicle of The Long Island College Hospital, 1993
Donald Frederick and Mildred Topp Othmer: A Commemorative of Their Lives and Legacies, 1999
Greater New York Hospital Association: Report to the public, 1971-1972
History and Genealogy of the Hoagland Family in America, 1891
A History of the Hoagland Laboratory, 1960
History of the Long Island College Hospital, Long Island College of Medicine, and the State University of New York College of Medicine at New York City, 1955
The Long Island College Hospital: General Alumni Catalogue, 1916
The Long Island College Hospital and its Graduates, 1899
The Long Island College Hospital and Training School for Nurses, 1858-1883-1933
The Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing: The Second Fifty Years: 1933-1983
Medical Education in Brooklyn: The First Hundred Years, 1960
Medical Education in the United States and Canada, 1990
Medical Society of the County of Kings: Sesquicentennial 1822-1972
Conditions Governing Access note
Open to researchers without restriction.
Historical note
The Long Island College Hospital (LICH) was founded in Brooklyn, New York, in 1858. The LICH Training School for Nurses, popularly known as the LICH School of Nursing, was established in 1883. Irene Sutcliffe, a graduate of the New York Hospital Training School, was selected to organize the school. The first class consisted of just three students. Irene Sutcliffe resigned her position in 1885 and was replaced by her twin sister, Ida Sutcliffe. During this period, the nurses' training program lasted two years, and there were no grades or examinations (the program would be expanded to three years in 1899).
The Alumnae Association of the Training School for Nurses was established in 1895. In 1904, Anne D. VanKirk replaced Isa Sutcliffe as head of the nursing school, and the school's training regimen was updated to conform with New York state guidelines. VanKirk was replaced by Miss E. Robinson, herself a graduate of the LICH School of Nursing, in 1920.
The school received temporary accreditation from the National League of Nursing in 1953. 1958 marked the first year that male students were admitted to the school. LICH became affiliated with Long Island University in 1960, which resulted in a new emphasis on academics at the nursing school (for the first time liberal arts were included in the school's curriculum). In 1962, the three year program was reduced back to a two year program (it would be shortened again to 22 months in 1975). The school switched academic affiliations twice in the ensuing years, to Packer Collegiate Institute in 1969 and then to St. Francis College in 1972.
In 1977 the school moved to St. Peter's School at 397 Hicks Street. The class of 1977 was the first to receive Associate of Applied Science (AAS) degrees. The school's academic affiliation changed once again in 1979 to Brooklyn College. Evening classes were first established in 1981, and primarily catered to men who chose nursing as a second career.
In May 2011, LICH became part of the SUNY Downstate Medical Center, and was renamed University Hospital of Brooklyn at Long Island College Hospital. Soon thereafter it was announced the LICH School of Nursing would no longer accept new students into its nursing program. The school officially closed in May 2013, and soon thereafter the Long Island College Hospital also closed.
Sources:
The Centennial: 1883-1983, Long Island College Hospital School of Nursing yearbook, 1983
History - Second Fifty Years - 1933-1983 - of the School of Nursing - Long Island College Hospital, 1983
LICHSON Chronicles, Spring 2013
Related Materials
Related archival collections at the Brooklyn Historical Society:
Missing Title
Frank J. Bramhall Civil War collection, 1860 – 1867 (1977.006)
Brooklyn Federation of Jewish Charities collection, 1910 – 1927 (1985.097)
Church Charity Foundation of Long Island publications, 1884 – 1951 (1985.113)
Ethel M. Martin Brooklyn nursing school collection, 1928 – 1933 (1996.001)
Elvira Hoffman papers, 1918 – 1918 (ARC.085)
Brooklyn hospitals and health services organizations collection, 1829 – 1998 (ARC.141)
Brooklyn Hospital records, circa 1845 - 1991 (ARC.225)
Brooklyn ephemera collection, 1814 – 1998 (ARC.272)
Elizabeth Feldhusen collection of Brooklyn ephemera, circa 1920s-1992 (ARC.299)
Photographs related to nurses can be found by searching for the subject "nurses" in the BHS image database available in the library reading room.
Newsletters; Memorabilia; Commemoratives; Commencement ceremonies |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Teaching hospitals |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Medicine |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Hospitals |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Posters; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Black-and-white prints (photographs); Color prints (photographs); Photographs; Artifacts (object genre); Nurses |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Cobble Hill (New York, N.Y.); Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.); Medicine |x Practice |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Nursing schools |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Nursing schools |x Alumni and alumnae |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Yearbooks; Articles of incorporation; Programs (documents); Minutes; Negatives (photographic); Digital Photographs; Long Island College Hospital. School of Nursing. Alumnae Association; Long Island College Hospital. School of Nursing; Prospect Heights Hospital (Brooklyn, New York, N.Y.). School of Nursing. Alumnae Association; Long Island College Hospital
- Series 1: Articles of incorporation and by-laws, 1903-1989; 15143; 0.1 Linear Feet in one folder
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains articles of incorporation, certificates of incorporation, and by-laws for the LICH School of Nursing Alumnae Association, dating from 1903, 1942, 1947, 1956, and 1989. It also includes the 1937 charter and by-laws of the Long Island College Hospital (with a 1945 amendment attached).
  - Articles of Incorporation and By-laws, 1903-1989; 15182 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Series 2: Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1895-1995; 15142; 0.25 Linear Feet in four folders
  The series contains LICH School of Nursing Alumnae Association meeting minutes. It includes two journals of general Alumnae Association meetings minutes (1895-1910), one journal of the association's Board of Directors meeting minutes (1903-1913), the Board President's notebook (1959-1974), and a set of typescripts and handwritten Board of Directors meeting minutes (1987, 1994-1995). The series also contains handwritten explanatory notes written by the donor to assist researchers.
  - Meeting minutes journals, 1895-1910; 15179 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes journal, 1903-1913; 15180 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors - President's book, 1959-1974; 15203 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1987, 1994-1995; 15181 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Series 3: Subject files, 1934-2010; 15150; 1 Linear Feet in two manuscript boxes
  The series contains administrative files, the bulk of which were created and maintained during the 1990s and 2000s, although they contain documents dating back to 1934. The files include lists of students from 1884 to 1989, Alumnae Association membership lists (1995-1996), correspondence, clippings, commencement addresses (1956, 1958), one financial report (1980), and other documents.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Accreditation self-study, 1985; 15195 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Active members lists, 1995; 15196 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Active members lists, 1996; 15197 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni - Class lists (1884-1989) (3 folders), circa 1950-1992; 15198 (Box 3, Folder 4-6)
  - Alumni - Complete list of graduates (1884-1936), circa 1956; 15199 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni - Complete list of graduates (1884-1997), circa 1997; 15200 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alumni inventory list, 1990; 15201 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Alumni officers, circa 1990; 15202 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1934-2006; 15204 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Clippings - Public relations, 2004-2005; 15205 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Commencements and other events, 1945-1963; 15206 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    General
    Includes typescripts of commencement addresses, graduating class lists, event calendars, meeting notes, and other documents.
  - Correspondence, 1982-2010; 15207 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fiftieth anniversary letter, 1998; 15208 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Financial report and deposit slips, 1980, 1986; 15209 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Historical notes, circa 1990s; 15210 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Holiday cards, 2005-2010; 15211 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Meeting news, 1987; 15212 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper ads, 1980-1994; 15213 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nursing pins, 1976-1995; 15214 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Silver inventory - Nurses' residence, 1974-1975; 15215 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Welcome PowerPoint for Class of 2001 (digital files)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    ID 2014_006_media_005. Access to digital materials is available onsite at the Othmer Library. Requests to access digital materials must be made at least 2 days in advance by emailing library@brooklynhistory.org.
- Series 4: Photographs, 1858-2013; 15149; 3 Linear Feet in seven boxes of various sizes, one oversize folder, and 3.91 gigabytes of digital files
  The series is intellectually arranged chronologically by date. Please note that dates are based on the content of the image, not the date the print was created (therefore, a 20th century copy of an 1894 class portait would be dated as 1894). The photographs are physically arranged by size and format.
  The series contains photographs and illustrations in a variety of formats (black-and-white prints, color prints, negatives, digital images, photocopies, and one slide) and sizes, dating from 1858 to 2013. It contains student portraits (classes and individuals), event photographs (graduation commencements, student recognition ceremonies, and other events), and promotional images used in publications.
  Class portraits cover the following years: 1891, circa 1894, 1903, 1906-1911, 1914-1924, 1926-1965, 1969, 1972, 1975, 1978, 1980-1982, 1985-1986, 1989, 1995, 2003, 2006, circa 2008, circa 2010.
  Additionally, a number of other group photographs can be found filed under various events from the 1960s through the 2000s.
  Common events which are documented include graduation commencements and proms, student recognization ceremonies (including capping and pinning ceremonies), pot-luck dinners, Atlantic Avenue parades and fairs, and cancer survivor events.
  The series contains one scrapbook which was assembled by Helen A. (Burgess) Gauthier (Class of 1920). It contains images of students, medical staff, friends, and LICH facilities, circa 1920.
  Additional photographs can be found in Series 8: Students, alumni, and faculty.
  - Buildings and interiors (photocopies), 1858-circa 1920s, 1999; 15266 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Various nurses and students (photocopies and copyprints), circa 1890s-1950s; 15267 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Class group portraits (oversize), 1891-1980; 15268 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Class group portraits, 1891-circa 2008; 15269 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Helen A. (Burgess) Gauthier photo albums, circa 1920; 15270 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Margaret Baird portrait, circa 1927; 15271 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - LICH nursing and surgery, circa 1930s-1940s; 15272 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Cadet Nurse Corps, 1942-1995; 15273 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Centennial ceremony, 1958; 15274 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Capping ceremony, circa 1960s; 15275 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Ethnic food event, circa 1960s; 15276 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Mrs. Hattie Osborn (Haines) - Class of 1895, circa 1960s; 15277 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Olive Haring celebration, circa 1960s; 15278 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Recreation, circa 1960s; 15279 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Snapshots, circa 1960s; 15280 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Promotional photographs, circa 1960s, 1972; 15281 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Promotional photographs, circa 1960s-1980s; 15283 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Olive Haring portraits, circa 1960s, 1990s; 15284 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Student portraits, 1969; 15285 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Class group portrait, circa 1970s; 15286 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Reunion celebration, circa 1970s; 15287 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Various events, circa 1970s-1990s; 15288 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Various events and snapshots, 1976-1990s; 15289 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Class group portrait, 1978; 15290 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Capping ceremony, 1979; 15291 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation, circa 1980s; 15292 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Nurses with Ronald Reagan cutout, circa 1980s; 15293 (Box 18, Folder -)
  - Party, circa 1980s; 15294 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / pinning ceremony, circa 1980s; 15295 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / pinning ceremony, circa 1980s; 15296 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Unidentified event/group portrait, circa 1980s; 15297 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation, circa 1980s-1990s; 15298 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Graduations, circa 1980s-1996; 15299 (Box 16, Folder -)
  - Capping ceremony, 1982; 15300 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation group portrait, 1985; 15301 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Class of 1986 group portraits, 15302 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - 1987 yearbook photographs (1 of 2), 1986-1987; 15303 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - 1987 yearbook photographs (2 of 2), 1986-1987; 15304 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation - May 28, 1987; 15305 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation - May 28, 1987; 15306 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Marie's bridal shower - May 29, 1987; 15307 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 1) - February 10, 1988; 15308 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 1) - February 10, 1988; 15309 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 2) - February 10, 1988; 15310 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 2) - February 10, 1988; 15311 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color - Roll 1) - June 2, 1988; 15312 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color - Roll 1) - June 2, 1988; 15313 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color - Roll 2) - June 2, 1988; 15314 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color - Roll 2) - June 2, 1988; 15315 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color - Roll 3) - June 2, 1988; 15316 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (B&W - Roll 1) - June 2, 1988; 15317 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (B&W - Roll 2) - June 2, 1988; 15318 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - LICH and surrounding locales (1988 yearbook photographs), 15319 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / capping ceremony (Color) - February 16, 1989; 15320 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / capping ceremony (B&W) - February 16, 1989; 15321 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / capping ceremony (B&W) - February 16, 1989; 15322 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Roll 1) - May 18, 1989; 15323 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Roll 1) - May 18, 1989; 15324 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Roll 2) - May 18, 1989; 15325 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Roll 2) - May 18, 1989; 15326 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color) - June 6, 1989; 15327 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Color) - June 6, 1989; 15328 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (B&W) - June 6, 1989; 15329 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (B&W) - June 6, 1989; 15330 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (1 of 2), circa 1990s; 15331 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (2 of 2), circa 1990s; 15332 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Party and Atlantic Avenue health screening, circa 1990s-2000s; 15333 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Party and Atlantic Avenue health screening, circa 1990s-2000s; 15334 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Rolls 1 and 2) - March 6, 1990; 15335 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Rolls 1 and 2) - March 6, 1990; 15336 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 3) - March 6, 1990; 15337 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 3) - March 6, 1990; 15338 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Rolls 1 and 2) - May 31, 1990; 15339 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner (Roll 1) - May 31, 1990; 15340 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Pot-luck dinner and Graduation (Roll 2) - May 31 and June 7, 1990; 15341 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Roll 3) - June 7, 1990; 15342 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation - June 7, 1990; 15343 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 2) - March 6, 1991; 15344 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (Roll 2) - March 6, 1991; 15345 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Pot luck dinner and Graduation (Roll 1) - June 4 and 6, 1991; 15346 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Roll 2) - June 6, 1991; 15347 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation (Roll 3) - June 6, 1991; 15348 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Atlantic Avenue event - May 10, 1992; 15350 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Atlantic Avenue event (Polaroids) - May 10, 1992; 15349 (Box 18, Folder -)
  - Various anniversaries and reunions, 1995-2005; 15351 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation, circa 1995; 15352 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony, 1996; 15353 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (B&W - Roll 1), 1996; 15354 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition ceremony (B&W - Roll 2), 1996; 15355 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation, 1996; 15356 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation, 1996; 15357 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation, 1998; 15358 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation, 1998; 15359 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation - June 3, 1999; 15360 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Graduation - June 3, 1999; 15361 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Graduation group portrait, circa 2000s; 15362 (Box 17, Folder -)
  - Graduation portraits, 2006-2007 (digital files)
    Digital material IDs 2014_006_media_004 (372 JPEG files). Access to digital materials is available onsite at the Othmer Library. Requests to access digital materials must be made at least 2 days in advance by emailing library@brooklynhistory.org.
  - Group portrait at entrance to Long Island College Hospital, 2000-2009 (digital files)
    One JPEG file, ID 2014_006_media_009. Access to digital materials is available onsite at the Othmer Library. Requests to access digital materials must be made at least 2 days in advance by emailing library@brooklynhistory.org.
  - Promise of Nursing gala - Feburary 7, 2001; 15363 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer Survivors Day - June 3, 2001; 15364 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer Survivors Day award - June 3, 2001; 15365 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Class of 2001 slideshow, 15366 (Box Digital files, Folder -)
  - Othmer Ambulatory Care Center group portraits - April 24, 2002; 15367 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer Survivors Day - June 2, 2002; 15368 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer survivors event - October, 2002; 15369 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer Survivors Day - June 1, 2003; 15370 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Cancer Survivors Day - June 4, 2004; 15371 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - "A Starry Night" - Othmer Cancer Center - July 29, 2004; 15372 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / pinning ceremony - September 9, 2004; 15373 (Box 19, Folder -)
  - Student government blood drive, 2004; 15374 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Alumni, 2004; 15375 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Student orientation, circa 2004; 15376 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Student orientation, circa 2004; 15377 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Poster presentations and lectures, circa 2004; 15378 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Promise of Nursing J and T Gala - March, 2005; 15379 (Box Digital files, Folder -)
  - Alumni Association luncheon and hospital tour - May, 2005; 15380 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Graduation - June, 2005; 15381 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - "A Starry Night" - Othmer Cancer Center - July 21, 2005; 15382 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Dinner event - August, 2005; 15383 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Student government blood drive - August, 2005; 15384 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Student government blood drive and other snapshots - August, 2005; 15385 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Student recognition / pinning ceremony - September, 2005; 15386 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Guild of LICH donation luncheon - November 14, 2005; 15387 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Teich Foundation luncheon - Fall, 2005; 15388 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Alumni celebration, 2005; 15389 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Janet Mackin birthday party, 2005; 15390 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Janet Mackin birthday party and other snapshots, 2005; 15391 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - 2005 yearbook photographs, 15392 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Nursing student presentations, circa 2005; 15393 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Graduation - June 6, 2006; 15394 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Reunion celebration - June 24, 2006; 15395 (Box 1, Folder -)
  - Teich Scholarship event, 2006; 15396 (Box 20, Folder -)
  - Class of 2006 student recognition ceremony, 15397 (Box Negative strips 1, Folder -)
  - Yearbook portraits, 2006; 15398 (Box Digital files, Folder -)